This is ridiculous.
What do you mean,
"I'll support you by your side"?
"Shut up and take my hand"?
This is so embarrassing.
Alya.
She did say "like", didn't she?
Is the dere attitude
she sometimes shows in Russian
not just a game?
I thought she was enjoying
the thrill of possibly getting caught.
But if that's what Alya really thinks...
No, it's impossible.
She must be like me,
saying the wrong thing
in the heat of the moment.
She must've come to her senses
and almost drowned
in shame and regret by now.
Yes, I have a feeling that's the case.
Work again?
You don't even come home.
Goodness, you're always like this.
Do you think an apology
will fix everything?
I feel like an idiot to worry about
such an uncertain
and vague emotion like love.
I will support her?
I, the one who dumped the burden
of the Suou family on Yuki and ran away?
That's funny.
Didn't she say she was busy?
No.
If what happened today
was a trap to get me
to join the student council,
she must be a part of it too.
What?
Masachika, you pervert!
You waited until the right time
to come out, didn't you?
Did you notice?
Of course I did.
You came out because you heard me
close the main door, didn't you?
Hey... wait a minute.
Aren't you curious why I'm doing this?
Anyway, put on some clothes first.
Don't be like that.
Let me explain, Masachika.
Actually, I just realized a grave matter.
A grave matter?
That's right.
We've been living together
for a long time,
but we haven't experienced
the "walk-in on someone changing event"!
That's worse than I thought!
Every brother in the world
wants to bump into
his sister changing, right?
That only works in 2D, you otaku brain!
I don't want to hear that from you!
And so, here's a fan service shot.
Oh, no.
Who are you talking to?
What?
The camera that idiots can't see.
Is it only for nude scenes?
All right. That's enough messing around.
I got you good today,
so this is my way of making it up to you.
Don't you dare apologize naked.
Hey, I just didn't talk back to you.
Why are you so full of yourself?
I know you've already checked me out
from head to toe and enjoyed it.
Yuki.
While we're at it,
I have to say this.
I'll go soft if it's full nudity.
Subtle sexiness is justice.
What?
I see.
That's indeed a blind spot.
Total victory.
Hey, wait.
You can't fool me.
You saw everything, right?
Clearly from head to toe, right?
I only saw boobs.
You finally admit it, you Boob Alien!
Shut up, you nympho!
By the way, Masachika.
What?
By the way,
why did you come to my room
to dry your hair so naturally?
Did you decide to join the student council
after talking to the president and Masha?
Well, about that...
I decided
to help Alya become
the student council president.
Alya snagged my brother
by sleeping with him!
No, I wasn't!
Damn it, you Boob Alien!
Does that mean
you're not satisfied with my C cup?
How could you be fooled so easily
by Alya's E cup (eyeballing)?
Don't say explicit things like cup sizes!
Calm down, brassiere.
No, brother.
A C-cup you can touch
is far better than
an E-cup you can't touch.
No, I can't touch either of them.
All right, bring it on!
Please be gentle with me!
Why are you so excited to try it?
Well, what are you going to do?
Should you take away
your sister's first boob touch?
Don't say that.
Just kidding.
After all, you took it away
when I was in elementary school.
I don't remember that.
What?
What? Are you serious?
Brother.
Have you forgotten?
That was when I was in second grade.
What?
While playing tag,
we bumped into each other.
Your face was planted
in the middle of my thigh
and your hand was squeezing my right boob!
I don't remember such a miracle happening!
Don't make up such
a ridiculous lucky perverted event!
You just clicked your tongue, right?
Seriously.
You had bad asthma at that time.
Basically, you couldn't go outside.
But I'm a healthy baby now.
I haven't caught a cold since junior high.
I'd rather you behave yourself.
Did I not?
Both at school and at home!
I'm sorry.
Don't apologize.
Spoil me more.
Thank you.
I see.
You've decided to run with Alya?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
It's nothing to apologize for.
A sibling rivalry is the way to go.
How passionate it'd be.
I'll tell you this just in case.
I'm not doing this because I hate you.
I know.
After all,
you love me the most, don't you?
I guess so.
You're blushing.
Shut up.
That's good enough.
Really?
Yes, thank you.
Well then.
From now on, we're rivals.
Right.
I don't mind you having an affair
with a girl who's at your beck and call.
If you ever get tired of Alya,
you can always change your mind
and come to me.
Wait, don't call it an affair.
I won't do that.
You'll come back to me in the end.
Are you some kind of perfect woman?
Good night.
Bye.
I see.
So you've finally found someone
who can motivate you...
Can't it be me?
Whatever, but
I won't lose.
Usually,
she would come here and make a scene.
Did I hurt her feelings yesterday?
She's not that kind of person.
But I have to make it up to her somehow.
Did you think I'd end it
with the serious part?
What a shame.
I'm a woman of my word!
Goodness, you're really...
Heave-ho.
What?
Pull me out.
Don't make me say it out loud.
It's embarrassing.
What are you doing?
Darn it. I'm going to bury you.
Darn you.
It's the stench of a man.
I'm going to get pregnant.
That's impossible!
Are you some kind of sheltered lady?
I am a sheltered lady.
What's wrong with that?
Good morning.
Did you watch yesterday's drama?
It was really good.
Yes, it made my heart flutter.
Why do I care so much?
I'm sure he'll come to school
with a sleepy face like always.
I'll just get along with him as usual.
Masachika, good morning.
Good morning, Masachika.
Good morning.
Good morning, Alya.
Kuze.
Are you previewing the material?
Yes.
What's the matter?
What? Nothing.
Is that so?
Masachika.
Takeshi and I were talking.
Should we go to karaoke sometime?
Sure. When?
Kuze seems kind of down.
He's giving off a somewhat ethereal vibe.
He even looks kind of cool.
What am I thinking?
It's nothing.
I'm sure he didn't get enough sleep again.
He isn't sleeping.
Why?
Is he really going to change
his habits for my sake?
From now on,
I'll support you by your side.
Kujou!
TEAM A, TEAM B
She's so cool!
Kujou is so amazing!
Kuze!
Hey, are you okay?
Your eyes are rolled back!
"The ball is my friend"
is just a fantasy.
I'm so hungry.
Kuze, are you all right?
Alya?
Why are you out here?
I was wondering if you were hurt.
You saw everything.
Are you all right?
Do you want to see the nurse?
No, I'm fine.
The gym was a bit hot,
so I came out for some fresh air.
I'll go back after a short rest.
I see.
Let me check.
What?
It's hard to tell like this.
Is... is that so?
E-cup.
Seriously?
No, wait.
If she was just eyeballing them,
could they be bigger?
What? A glimpse of the armpit?
Damn it, did you do that on purpose?
Yuki! This is what I meant.
Sure enough, subtle sexiness is justice!
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Anyway, you'd better drink some water.
What? Wait, Kuze.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
I just wanted to clear my head physically.
I-I see.
Oh my, Kuze?
What's wrong?
Are you trying to be a sweaty hunk?
Hello, Masha.
I just wanted to clear my head.
Don't worry.
What is it?
Is something in the sky?
Clouds.
You're right.
Why are you stating the obvious?
Gym uniform is good stuff.
You're soaking wet.
Do you have a towel?
No, I don't.
But it'll dry up naturally.
Come on, lower your head.
What's going on?
I didn't know such an event existed!
Okay, it's dry.
How is it? Do you feel more refreshed?
Yes, I do.
I think I know how it feels to be a dog.
Are you an Akita Inu?
No, I don't know breeds.
I'm sorry.
I'm just an uncultured mutt.
Mischievous dogs are cute too.
That's enough. Let's go back, Kuze.
Masha, shouldn't you go back to class too?
Hey, I just got here.
We're going back.
Okay.
See you after school.
Okay, see you after school.
Thanks for the towel.
I know what this is.
It's the part where I'd be
called "dirty" or "obscene."
So, are you okay now?
What?
The spot where you got hit by the ball.
Are you sure you don't need ice on it?
She thought I was using
cold water to ice my wound!
No, I'm fine.
It's not swollen anyway.
Really?
No need. I'm really fine.
What's going on?
Why is she being so gentle to me?
The dere period?
Is this the dere period?
Alya.
You seem to be especially
gentle to me today.
That's because you've been a bit down
since this morning.
I'm just a bit worried
that something happened to you.
Just as I thought,
is it because of what happened yesterday?
No, I'm not feeling down.
I just didn't have breakfast.
I was wondering why you
were so focused in class today.
It turns out you couldn't sleep
because you were hungry.
No, that's because
I had a good night's sleep.
I see, a good night's sleep.
But I couldn't sleep because of you.
In the end, this unserious
and happy-go-lucky guy
could sleep like it was nothing.
I see!
Well, Alya, listen carefully.
This is what God said.
What is it?
Don't tell me you're going to say,
"Love your neighbors."
No.
This is what God said.
If someone hits you on the right,
turn your cheek
and let them hit you on the left.
Goodness.
Is that the look you give
to a masochist swine?
It's a look I give
to a frivolous good-for-nothing.
Goodness.
I was worried for nothing.
He's the worst.
I knew I wouldn't fall
for a frivolous guy like him.
Thank goodness.
It's the usual Alya.
Alya.
Do you want to go
to the student council office with me?
Maybe I went too far.
-We shall take our leave!
The same guys
from the baseball and soccer club?
Sorry to bother you.
I'm sorry, I got the wrong place.
I'm sorry.
I thought the people from the baseball
and soccer clubs came back.
Well, what did they do?
My cute junior went
to mediate their disputes.
But they didn't listen to advice
and continued
their embarrassing bickering, didn't they?
That's why I gave them a slight...
A slight warning.
I see.
No, but... isn't using
a bamboo sword too much?
D-Don't worry.
I can kill with my fists,
but I've never killed anyone
with a bamboo sword.
I see.
That's because the bamboo sword
will break before that.
I think I once heard a guy
call Sarashina "boss lady."
I see it now.
Touya!
You don't have to be so nervous, Kuze.
Chisaki didn't use violence on them.
She just threatened them
with her violent background.
Hold on, Touya.
Goodness.
I'm sorry.
What a heartwarming interaction.
Come on.
Goodness.
-Chisaki.
-Goodness.
You'll dislocate my shoulder.
-You'll dislocate it.
-Idiot.
It's heart... warming?
I'm sorry.
Am I too late?
Goodness.
That's enough fooling around
in the student council office.
No, it's not like that.
I'm sorry. Does it hurt?
I'm fine.
My shoulders were a bit stiff,
so it was perfect.
I'm really sorry.
I can never get the right amount of force.
Which warrior tribe are you from?
It's fine.
This is what I've been working out for.
Just bring it on.
Touya...
What?
Was there a trigger for this sweet mood?
Goodness, you're going too far.
Say,
if Chisaki is called Boss Lady,
does she bind her chest in sarashi?
Why would you think that?
No, if that's the case,
she'll be Sarashina in sarashi.
My goodness. You two are so close.
No, we're not.
It seems we can't hide it
from your sister.
What?
Our close relationship.
Shut up.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
I'm a little late.
Don't worry about it, Suou.
Well then,
let's start the student council meeting.
-Let's do our best.
Well then, Kuze,
could you introduce yourself
to everyone again?
Yes.
I'm honored to join the student council
as the general affairs officer.
I'm Masachika Kuze.
Next year, I plan to join Alisa Kujou
for the student council
president election.
I look forward to working with all of you.